drugstoreawakening.com 2012-03-14

# US Drugs - Privacy Policy

At US Drugs Ltd, we are committed to ensuring your online privacy, and this guides every decision we make about how, where, and when to collect your personally identifiable information on our website. Our site meets stringent security and privacy standards for both e-commerce and personal information. We have provided this notice to describe the online information collection and use practices at US Drugs Ltd. This document describes the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. This privacy policy applies only to the information collected by US Drugs Ltd and does not apply to any other information that US Drugs Ltd collects about you. If you have any questions or concerns about this statement, or about the way your information is collected and used, please Contact Us.

Any changes in our Privacy Policy will appear on this page so that you are aware of the data we collect and how we use it. If provide us with a valid email address, we will notify you by email of any significant changes to this Privacy Policy. You will be given the opportunity to opt in to any significant new uses of personal information if that information was collected prior to the change in this policy. If you do not opt in to any significant new uses of your personal information, that information will continue to be governed by the policy in effect at the time your information was collected.

## Our Privacy Guarantee

US Drugs Ltd site is owned and operated by US Drugs Ltd. We are the sole owner of our customers’ personally identifiable information. Your personally identifiable information is information that can be used to contact or identify you. Your name, home address, telephone number, and email address are examples of personally identifiable information. We do not sell, rent, loan or give your personal information to any non-affiliated third parties, except as described in this Policy. We may transfer your personal information to companies that perform services on our behalf or, if you opt in, to companies whom we believe may offer you related services or products that may be of interest to you. We notify businesses to which we transfer your personal information that the information was shared with us under this Privacy Policy. If you tell us that you do not wish to have this information used for further contact, we will remove you from our distribution list. With a customer’s permission or if a customer chooses to use the services of our partners, we may pass certain personally identifiable information to partners. We may also share non-personally identifiable information with partners as, for example, with fulfilment house or other businesses that help us provide services to you. Please read more about the Use Of Information by Third Party Partners in this document.

## Who May Use This Site

This Site is not intended or designed to attract users under the age of 13. We do not collect personally identifiable data from any person we know to be under the age of 13 and instruct users under 13 not to send us any information to this Site.

We may link information collected from you through various means, including information collected automatically and through the use of cookies and Registered User information, with information we learn in our stores and from Registered Users. Our goal is to help offer you content, advertisements, products, and services that are most likely to appeal to you.

## Information Use

Information you provide is used in order to respond to your request. For example, to fulfill your order or contact you with information about your order, to send you email alerts, or to send you newsletters. From time to time US Drugs Ltd requests information from users via surveys on our site. Participation in these surveys is voluntary, and information collected as part of those surveys is used in compliance with this privacy policy.

In the event that US Drugs Ltd or some of our assets are sold or transferred or used as security or to the extent we engage in business negotiations with our business partners, the information collected on this Site may be transferred or shared with third parties as part of that transaction or negotiation. We may also provide information or provide access to information to any of our affiliated businesses or to our business partners or fulfilment houses.

## Links

US Drugs Ltd site may contain links to other websites not operated by US Drugs Ltd. These links are provided as a convenience and do not constitute an affiliation with, endorsement or sponsorship of the third parties that operate those websites. US Drugs Ltd is not responsible for the availability or reliability of the content of these third party websites. Any information you provide to those third parties is not subject to the terms of this privacy policy, and US Drugs Ltd is not responsible for the treatment of the information you provide to those third parties. We recommend that you review the privacy policy of that third party, and of any third party to whom you provide personally identifiable information online.

## How We Keep Your Information Secure

We use state-of-the-art security measures to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. Specifically, we use Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology for the areas of our site where we ask you to provide personally identifiable information. SSL technology provides for the safe transmission of personal information you give us because the information is encrypted. Encryption involves systematically scrambling numbers and letters so that if someone managed to intercept a packet of information, they would not be able to make sense of it. Although encryption slows the process of sending information across the Internet, it does provide better protection for your information.

You can tell you have entered a secured area when you look at the Universal Resource Locator (URL) in your browser’s address bar and see that it has «https://» before the rest of the Web address. The «s» means that the page is hosted from a secured server. We use secured servers for our Order processing pages, and special promotions. Unsecured pages have URLs that begin with «http://» (without the «s»). Most of our shopping aisles and health information areas are hosted from servers that do not use SSL. Since we do not collect personal information in these areas, using regular servers ensures a faster browsing experience.

You may on occasion encounter a standard warning that many browsers display when a visitor moves from a «secured» page to an «unsecured» page. When you encounter such a warning on our Web site, it usually means that you are moving from an «https://» to an «http://» page. If you see other browser warnings or error messages concerning the security of our site, please Contact Us. Include the specific wording you saw and where at US Drugs Ltd you encountered the message. Providing us with these details helps us to know if you have encountered a technical difficulty or a standard warning like the one described above.

If you use this site, you are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your access information and password and for restricting access to your computer and you agree to accept responsibility for all activities that occur under your password.

## Cookies

Like many other websites, we also collect information about site traffic and usage patterns through the use of cookies and Web server logs. Cookies are small computer files we transfer to your computer’s hard drive. These small text files help us personalize content on our pages and provide programs like e-coupons. Your browser software can be set to reject or accept cookies. Instructions for resetting the browser are available in the Help section of most browsers.

Our use of cookies also allows us to collect and retain certain information about a website user, such as the type of Web browser used by our customer. This information is not linked to personally identifiable information about a particular individual or customer account, but it is collected from a particular computer as the user moves through a website.

Reviewing our Web server logs and our customers’ use of our site helps us to statistically monitor how many people are using our site and for what purpose. Only authorized US Drugs Ltd personnel have access to the Web server logs, cookie utilization data, and purchase history information collected by us. These employees are held to strict confidentiality and security policies and procedures.

## Spyware

Spyware is a data collection technology that is downloaded to a consumer’s personal computer which aids in gathering information about that person or organization without their knowledge. It can enter your computer as a software virus or as a result of installing a new program. It is used to gather information about your personal internet usage, monitor keyboard strokes or capture personal information for use by other parties.

US Drugs Ltd does not install any tracking software or spyware on your system, or collect personal information about you and your browsing habits. Any personally identifiable information gathered about users is with the consent of the user, and all possible uses for the data are outlined at the time the data is provided. We take the security of your personal information seriously, and work hard to maintain a safe and secure site for your use.

## Your Consent

We hope you’ll agree to let us contact you with timely promotional offers. You can take yourself off our email list for promotional offers at any time by contacting us using Customer Support Ticket System.

You can request the removal or modification of your Personal Information by sending an email to the appropriate area under «Contact Us». You may also request that we not disclose your information. We will respond to accommodate your request in 30 days. It would be helpful to let us know the context in which you provided Personal Information.

## Contact Information

If you have any questions or concerns about this statement, or about the way your information is collected and used, please [Contact Us](http://drugstoreawakening.com/contacts/form/).
